Kevin Gerstner



☑ sirkevinicus@gmail.com

github.com/SirKevinicus

314-614-2301

Work Experience

Graphic Design Intern @ ArchCity Defenders

MAY 2019 - AUG 2019 \\ SAINT LOUIS, MO

- » Created a digital art collection of clients using Photoshop for print and web marketing.
- » Illustrated graphics that were featured on the companies' social media pages.
- » Researched social justice issues and communicated key issues to affected communities.

Research Assistant @ University of Tulsa

OCT 2018 - APR 2019 \\ TULSA, OK

Researched and co-authored a paper on the topic of HCI and Gender with Prof. Sandeep Kuttal entitled: "Remote Pair-Programming in Online CS Education: Investigating through a Gender Lens". The paper was presented in the 2019 VL/HCC (Visual Languages & Human Centric Computing) conference.

Game Navigator & Server @ Shuffles Board Game Café

SEP 2018 - JAN 2019 \\ TULSA, OK

Taught groups of people how to play board games, as well as taking orders and delivering food. In my spare time, I read rule books to learn new games.

Projects

Tomb of Khaibit

Game Programmer \\ 2021

- » Coded a procedurally generated dungeon using an original algorithm
- » Directed sub-teams to create features like Networking, UI, Puzzles, & Enemies
- » Used Agile scrum workflow, Git for project management, and utilzed Design Documents

Song Pong

Feature Developer & Artist \\ 2020

- » Made a rhythm game based on Pong in three months with the Unity engine
- » Coded features like spawning notes along to the beat and a Song Editor
- » Created art assets in Illustrator and Blender

Portfolio Website

Web Developer \\ 2021 \\ www.kevingerstner.com

- » Designed and coded a portfolio website using HTML, CSS/SASS, Bootstrap 5, and JS
- » Used web-friendly standards like Responsive Design and Lighthouse Analytics

Knock-Out! Global Smackdown Board Game

Board Game Designer & Artist \\ 2018

- Created over 150 unique card illustrations, box art, and graphics for marketing
- » Created a Wordpress website
- » Launched a Kickstarter campaign

Summary

Passionate, well-rounded software developer with experience building projects in C#, Java, and C++. Has developed websites with HTML, SASS, JS, and jQuery. Will graduate in 2021 with a B.S. in Computer Science and Minors in Art & Math. Specializes in leading teams with Agile workflows to create ambitious and creative projects. Picks up new skills quickly.

Skills

Programming

C++ • Java • C# • OpenGL • HTML • CSS/SASS • jQuery • JavaScript

Tools & Platforms

Unity • GitHub • Netlify • WordPress • itch.io • Visual Studio • ClickUp • Eclipse

Design

Photoshop • Illustrator • InDesign • XD • Figma • Aseprite

Education

The University of Tulsa 2017 - 2021 \\ TULSA, OK

B.S. in Computer Science and B.S. in Computer Simulation and Gaming with Math and Art minors. 3.8 GPA

Certifications

Unity Certified Associate Game Developer

Interests

Board Games, Overwatch, Art, Animated movies, Horror Games, Music, Coffee Tasting